A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Historical Collections, Claude Moore Health Sciences Library, University of Virginia
HEDO
The collection comprises 61 boxes of archival material.
The Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) papers are composed of 61 boxes of archival material, including photographs and manuscripts.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
The Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) papers are composed of 61 boxes of archival material, including photographs and manuscripts. The HEDO collection documents the history of the University of Virginia Hospital, its physical grounds, its staff, its policies, and operating procedures with some records that go back to 1919. One of the most important aspects of this collection are the Minutes of the Executive Committee of the UVa Hospital, which date back to 1920. The HEDO collection also boasts the minutes from many of the Hospital Committees set up to monitor particular issues germane to hospital administration. Among the hospital committees whose minutes are included in the HEDO collection are the Preventorium Committee, the Civil Rights Committee, the Infections Committee, the Accreditation Advisory Committee, the Clinical Staff Committee, the Administrative Staff Committee, the Medical Advisory Committee, and the Governor's Committee on Nursing. Documents from the Joint Commission on Accreditation of Hospitals covering the 1950s through the 1980s, as well as the American College of Surgeons Hospital Standardization Scoring Report for 1948, are included.
Other highlights of the HEDO collection include statistical records of the number of patients admitted to the UVa Hospital every year, the number of operations performed each year, as well as rates for various medical services. The HEDO Collection contains a wealth of information on the University of Virginia Hospital, from the mundane(e.g. the menus for the hospital's cafeteria), to the sublime (including policy statements on controversial issues such as sterilization, abortion, and civil rights.
Contents List
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF UVA HOSPITAL February 22, 1944, TM (1) (Box-folder 1:001)
  PRESENT: DRS. NEFF, ROYSTER, SMITH, BRAY AND HOUGH
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL March 7, 1924, TM w/autograph corrections (Box-folder 1:002)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL April 1924, TM (Box-folder 1:003)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL May 1924 - July 1924, TM w/ autograph corrections (1) (Box-folder 1:004)
- LETTER:RE: STAFF PETITION IN SUPPORT OF EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE October 19, 1931 (Box-folder 1:005)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL October - December 1931, TM (5) (Box-folder 1:006)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL March - December 1932, TM (Box-folder 1:007)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE TO UVA HOSPITAL October - December 1932, TL, TLS, TL (carbon) (Box-folder 1:008)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL February - December 1933, TM (Box-folder 1:009)
- MEMORANDUM FOR THE DEAN AND MEMBERS OF THE CLINICAL STAFF August 31, 1933, TM (carbon) (Box-folder 1:010)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January - December 1934, TM (Box-folder 1:011)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January - December 1935, TMS (Box-folder 1:012)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL October - December 1936, TM (Box-folder 1:013)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL April - December 1937, TM (Box-folder 1:014)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1937, TLS (& carbon copy), TL (Box-folder 1:015)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL February - December 1938, TM (Box-folder 1:016)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE March - December 1938, TLS, TLS w/ Autograph notes, TL (carbon) (Box-folder 1:017)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL February - December 1939, TM (10) (Box-folder 1:018)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1939, TLS, TL (carbon) (Box-folder 1:019)
- PROPOSAL FOR REARRANGING THE MEDICAL INTERNSHIP November 1939, TM (Box-folder 1:020)
- TRUST AGREEMENT: WILLIAM J. RUCKER TO GEORGE PAUSCH & W. ALLAN PERKINS, TRUSTEES April 19, 1939, MIMEOGRAPH, TM (Box-folder 1:021)
- RATE TABLES, REPORT OF RECORD ROOM COMMITTEE, ANTI-CONVULSIVE CLINIC Circa 1939-1946, TM (carbon), TM, Mimeograph, AM, Brochure (Box-folder 1:022)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January - December 1940, TM (Box-folder 1:023)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1940, TLS (3), TL (2), TM (Box-folder 1:024)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1941, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:025)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL 1941, TM (2), TL (Box-folder 1:026)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL March - September 1942, TM (Box-folder 1:027)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1942, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:028)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January - November 1943, TM (Box-folder 1:029)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1943, TL (2), TLS (1), AM (Box-folder 1:030)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL February - September 1944, TM (Box-folder 1:031)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1944, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:032)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL February - December 1945, TM (Box-folder 1:033)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE 1945, TL (2), TM, TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:034)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL 1946, TM (Box-folder 1:035)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE January - March 1946, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:036)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE April - September 1946, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:037)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE October - December 1946, TL (2), TLS (2), ALS (1) (Box-folder 1:038)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL 1947, TM (Box-folder 1:039)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE January - March 1947, TL (2), TLS (2), ALS (Box-folder 1:040)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE April - June 1947, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:041)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE July - September 1947, TL (2), TLS (2), AM (Box-folder 1:042)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE October - November 1947, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:043)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE December 1947, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 1:044)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL 1948, TM (Box-folder 2:001)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE January - February 1948, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:002)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE March - April 1948, TL (2), TLS (2), ALS (1) (Box-folder 2:003)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE May 1948, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:004)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE June - July 1948, TL (2), TLS (3), TM (1) (Box-folder 2:005)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE August 1948, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:006)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE September 1948, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:007)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE October 1948, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:008)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE November - December 1948, TL (2), TLS (2), TM (1) (Box-folder 2:009)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January - April 1949, TM (Box-folder 2:010)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL May - December 1949, TM (Box-folder 2:011)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January 1949, TM (Box-folder 2:012)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE January 1949, TL (2), TLS (2), TM (1), ALS (1) (Box-folder 2:013)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE February 1949, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:014)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAOL CORRESPONDENCE March - April 1949, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:015)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE May - June 1949, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:016)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE July - December 1949, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:017)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January - June 1950, TM (Box-folder 2:018)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL July - December 1950, TM (Box-folder 2:019)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE January - March 1950, TL (2), ALS (1), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:020)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE April - June 1950, TL (2), TLS (2), TM (Box-folder 2:021)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE July - August 1950, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:022)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE September 1950, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:023)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE October - December 1950, TL (2), TLS (3) (Box-folder 2:024)
- MINUTES OF THE EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL January 1951, TM (Box-folder 2:025)
- EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF THE UVA HOSPITAL CORRESPONDENCE January 1951, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 2:026)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER, UVA HOSPITAL 1953 - 1954, TM, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 3:001)
  CORRESPONDENCE AND COST ESTIMATES
- PROPOSED CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1955, TL (3), TLS (2) (Box-folder 3:002)
  CORRESPONDENCE WITH DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
- PROPOSED PROGRAM TO PREPARE TEACHERS OF SPECIAL EDUCATION...AT UVA 1955, TLS, TM (Box-folder 3:003)
- SPECIFICATIONS: CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER AT UVA March 1, 1956, TM (Box-folder 3:004)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE & COST ESTIMATES January - May 1956, TL (2), TLS (2), TM (1), ALS (1) (Box-folder 3:005)
  INCLUDES PROJECT CONSTRUCTION
- CONSTRUCTION OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER June - December 1956, TL (2), TLS (2), TM (Box-folder 3:006)
  CORRESPONDENCE, PROPOSALS, APPLICATIONS
- LOG ON CHILDREN'S CONVALESCENT HOME, UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL 1956, TM (Box-folder 3:007)
  RECORD ON DAILY PROGRESS OF CONSTRUCTION & OF WEATHER CONDITIONS
- CONSTRUCTION & OPENING OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1957, TL (3), TLS (2), TM (2) (Box-folder 3:008)
  CORRESPONDENCE, COST ESTIMATES, MEMORANDA
- LOG ON CHILDREN'S CONVALESCENT HOME, UVA HOSPITAL 1957, TM (Box-folder 3:009)
  RECORD OF DAILY PROGRESS OF CONSTRUCTION AND WEATHER CONDITIONS
- UVA MEDICAL ALUMNI ASSOCIATION NEWSLETTER October - November 1957, Magazine (Box-folder 3:010)
  CHILDRENS' REHABILITATION CENTER OPENS
- AN INTRODUCTION TO THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER November 1957, TM (Box-folder 3:011)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE 1958, TL (2), TLS (2), ALS (1), TM (2) (Box-folder 3:012)
- REPORTS ON CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER OF UVA 1958, TM (Box-folder 3:013)
  REPORTS FROM ADMINISTRATORS, NURSING SERVICE, MEDICAL ADVISORY BOARD
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND PAPERS 1959, TL (2), TLS (2), TM (2) (Box-folder 3:014)
- MINUTES OF THE REHABILITATION COMMITTEE OF THE C. R. CENTER June - July 1959, TM (Box-folder 3:015)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND PAPERS 1960, TLS (2), TL (1), Memos (Box-folder 3:016)
- REPORT ON THE TEACHING PROGRAM AT THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1960, TM (Box-folder 3:017)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE 1961, TLS (1), TM (1) (Box-folder 3:018)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND CONFERENCE NOTES 1962, TLS, TM, TL, ALS (Box-folder 3:019)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1963, TLS (2), TM (1), TL (1) (Box-folder 3:020)
- RESEARCH AND TRAINING CENTER: MEMORANDUM OF A MEETING October 25, 1963, TM (Box-folder 3:021)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1964, TL (2), TLS (2), ALS (1), TM (1) (Box-folder 3:022)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1965, TLS (2), TL (1), TM (Box-folder 3:023)
- APPLICATION FOR CHILDHOOD ACCIDENT RESEARCH CONFERENCE GRANT 1965, Mimeograph, TM (Box-folder 3:024)
- PEDIATRIC FACILITIES: RESEARCH & TRAINING CENTER FOR EXCEPTIONAL CHILDREN December 1965, TM & xerox, TM, TL (Box-folder 3:025)
- FEDERAL AID TO REHABILITATION FACILITIES AND WORKSHOPS December 27, 1965, TLS (1), TD (1) (Box-folder 3:026)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1966, TLS (3), TL (2) (Box-folder 3:027)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILIATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1967, TLS (3), TL (1) (Box-folder 3:028)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1968, TLS (2), TL (1), ALS (1) (Box-folder 3:029)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER: STAFF LISTINGS, SALARIES, SCHEDULES, ETC. December 1968, TM (2), AM (1) (Box-folder 3:030)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1968 1968, TM (Box-folder 3:031)
  INCLUDES REPORT FOR THE YEAR: STATISTICS ON PATIENTS & SUMMARY OF CRC ACTIVITIES
- TARGET TENNIS, INCLUDING A SPECIAL SECTION ON THE NEW ADAPTED RAQUET FOR THE SEVERLY HANDICAPPED CHILD September 1968, TM (8) (Box-folder 3:032)
- WHEELCHAIR BOWLING WITH SPECIAL REFERENCE TO THE ADAPTER PUSHER DEVICE September 1968, TM (11) (Box-folder 3:033)
- ARCHERY FOR THE PHYSICALLY HANDICAPPED CHILD & INTRODUCTION TO THE NEW AMPUTEE ADAPTOR DEVICE September 1968, Mimeograph, TM (Box-folder 3:034)
- WHEELCHAIR FENCING September 1968, TM (11) (Box-folder 3:035)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1969, TLS (3), TL (1), AL (1) (Box-folder 4:001)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER STATISTICAL REPORT January 1969, TM (Box-folder 4:002)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER SPACE AND ORGANIZATION June 23, 1969, TL, Xerox of Floor plans, TMemo (Box-folder 4:003)
- OPERATING FUND REPORT FOR CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1969, TLS, TMemo (Box-folder 4:004)
- REPORT OF CURRENT OPERATIONS FOR THE TWO MONTHS PERIOD ENDED 8-31-69 1969, TLS, TMemo (Box-folder 4:005)
- CHLDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER REPORT 1969, TMemo (Box-folder 4:006)
  EVALUATION OF THE CENTER & RECOMMENDATIONS FOR FUTURE PROJECTS
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA January 1970-May 8, 1970, TLS (2), TL (2), ALS (1), TM (Box-folder 4:007)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA May 13 1970-December 1970, TLS (3), TL (1) (Box-folder 4:008)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER GENERAL DESCRIPTION September 1970, TMemo (Box-folder 4:009)
- ANALYSIS OF THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION RESEARCH CENTER 1970, TM (2), TLS (1) (Box-folder 4:010)
- RECORD OF STAFF CONFERENCE FOR THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1970, TM (Box-folder 4:011)
  REMOVED BECAUSE OF HIPPA: RECORDS PATIENT'S NAMES, AGES, DIAGNOSIS, ETC.
- APPLICATION FOR FEDERAL ASSISTANCE FOR THE EDUCATION OF HANDICAPPED CHILDREN 1970, TM (Box-folder 4:012)
  APPLICATION FORM & PROJECT INFORMATION, STATEMENT OF ASSURANCES
- INTER-CLINIC INFORMATION BULLETIN February 1970, Pamphlet (Box-folder 4:013)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA January 1971 - June 1971, TLS (3), TL (2) (Box-folder 4:014)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA June 1971 - December 1971, TLS (3), TL (3) (Box-folder 4:015)
- PROGRAM FOR C.R.C.-14TH ANNIVERSARY GRAND OPENING CELEBRATION December 1971, TM (Box-folder 4:016)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1972, TL (3), TLS (3) (Box-folder 4:017)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE 1973, TLS (2), TL (2), TMemo (1) (Box-folder 4:018)
- STATISTICAL REPORT & SPACE ALLOCATION REPORT/PATIENTS AT C.R.C. 1968-1973 September 1973, TL, TM, Chart, Drawings (Box-folder 4:019)
- REPORTS ON CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1971-1973 1973, TLS, TM (Box-folder 4:020)
  INCLUDES COST REPORTS, OPERATING FUND REPORTS, STATISTICS, ETC.
- HIRING KURT OPPELT 1973, TLS, TM, Article Offprint (Box-folder 4:021)
  3 ARTICLES BY OPPELT
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1974, TLS (3), TL (2), TM (1), charts (Box-folder 4:022)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1975, TLS (2), TL (1) (Box-folder 4:023)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER MEMORANDA 1978, TL (xerox) (Box-folder 4:024)
- MINUTES, MEMORANDA & CORRESPONDENCE TO THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER ADVISORY COMMITTEE 1969, TM (4), TL (1) (Box-folder 4:025)
- MINUTES, MEMORANDA & CORRESPONDENCE TO THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER ADVISORY COMMITTEE 1970, TLS (3), AL (1), TM (1) (Box-folder 4:026)
- MINUTES, MEMORANDA & CORRESPONDENCE TO THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER ADVISORY COMMITTEE 1971, TL (2), TLS (1), TM (Box-folder 4:027)
- MINUTES OF THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER ADVISORY COMMITTEE June 13, 1974, TM (Box-folder 4:028)
- CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER BUDGETS 1956 - 1973, AM, TM, TLS (Box-folder 4:029)
  COST REPORTS, CONTRIBUTION REPORTS, OPERATING FUND REPORTS, PROPOSED BUDGETS
- PROJECT CONSTRUCTION APPLICATION FOR UVA CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER ?1957, TM (Box-folder 4:030)
- PROPOSED FACILITIES FOR THE EDUCATION OF THE HANDICAPPED C.R.C May 1957, TLS, TM (Box-folder 4:031)
  TENTATIVE SPECIAL EDUCATION PROPOSAL
- PROJECT CRITERIA: RESEARCH & TRAINING CENTER FOR EXCEPTIONAL CHILDREN 1963 - 1966, TL, TM (Box-folder 4:032)
- ADDITIONS TO & RENOVATIONS OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1967 - 1968, TLS (2), TL (1), TM (Box-folder 4:033)
- PROPOSED ADDITION TO THE CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER May 1968, TM (2) (Box-folder 4:034)
- PROJECT DESCRIPTION FOR C.R.C. PROPOSED ADDITION August 5, 1968, TM (2) (Box-folder 4:035)
  INCLUDES APPLICATION FOR PROPOSED CONSTRUCTION
- GRANT & PROJECT APPLICATIONS FOR C.R.C. ADDITION & EXPANSION August 6, 1968, TM, TLS (Box-folder 4:036)
- THE VIRGINIA CLUB WOMAN 1968, Magazine (Box-folder 4:037)
  CONTAINS ARTICLE ON PROPOSED C.R.C. SWIMMING POOL
- ADDITIONS & EXPANSION OF C.R.C.: CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1969, TL (3), TLS (3) (Box-folder 4:038)
- OUTLINE SPECIFICATION ADDITION FOR CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER June 27, 1969, TM (Box-folder 4:039)
- LEGAL DESCRIPTION OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER & DEED September 1969, TLS, TM, Maps (Box-folder 4:040)
- PRELIMINARY PLANS & OUTLINE SPECIFICATIONS FOR CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER September 1969, TLS, TL, Maps (Box-folder 4:041)
- ADDITIONS TO & EXPANSION OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER: CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1970, TLS (2), TL, TM (Box-folder 4:042)
- EXPANSION OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER 1970, TM, Xerox Document (Box-folder 4:043)
  PROPOSAL, POWER OF ATTORNEY FORM, COST & CONSTRUCTION DATA REPORT
- ADDITIONS TO & EXPANSION OF CHILDREN'S REHABILITATION CENTER: CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1971 - 1972, TLS (2), Xerox Document (Box-folder 4:044)
- PROCEDURE MANUAL: MEDICAL RECORD DEPARTMENT, UVA HOSPITAL 1959, Carbon Copy & Mimeograph TMs (Box-folder 5:001)
  ADMINISTRATIVE, INSURANCE, DISCHARGE, CODINE STUDY & INDEXING PROCEDURES
- OPERATING REPORT: UVA HOSPITAL DIVISION, FOR YEAR 1940 1949, Mimeograph TMs, TLS (Box-folder 5:002)
- COVER LETTER FOR OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR 1950 October 3, 1950, TL (Box-folder 5:003)
- OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR YEAR ENDED JUNE 30, 1952 1952, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 5:004)
- CORRESPONDENCE October 8, 1956, TLS (Box-folder 5:005)
- OPERATING REPORT FOR UVA HOSPITAL FOR YEAR ENDED JUNE 30, 1964 1964, TMs (Box-folder 5:006)
- OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR YEAR ENDED JUNE 30, 1965 1965, TMs (Box-folder 5:007)
- OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR 6 MONTHS PERIOD ENDING 12-31-65 1965, TMs (Box-folder 5:008)
- OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR YEAR ENDED JUNE 30, 1966 1966, TMs (Box-folder 5:009)
- OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR THE 6 MONTH'S PERIOD ENDED 12-31-67 1967, TM (Box-folder 5:010)
- OPERATING REPORT OF UVA HOSPITAL FOR YEAR ENDED JUNE 30, 1970 1970, TMs (Box-folder 5:011)
- REPORT OF CURRENT OPERATIONS FOR 6 MONTH PERIOD ENDED 12-31-72 January 1973, TMs (Box-folder 5:012)
- REPORT OF CURRENT OPERATIONS FOR 8 MONTH PERIOD ENDED 2-28-79 February 1974, TLS (1), TMs (Box-folder 5:013)
- OPERATING BUDGET: UVA HOSPITAL, 1952 - 1953 1952 - 1953, TMs (Box-folder 5:014)
- OPERATING BUDGET: UVA HOSPITAL, 1957 - 1958 1957 - 1958, TMs (Box-folder 5:015)
- OPERATING BUDGET: UVA HOSPITAL 1959 - 1960 1959 - 1966, TMs (Box-folder 5:016)
- OPERATING BUDGET: UVA HOSPITAL, 1960 -1961 1960 - 1961, TMs (Box-folder 5:017)
- OPERATING BUDGET: UVA HOSPITAL, 1961 - 1962 1961 - 1962, TMs (Box-folder 5:018)
- RATE STRUCTURE BOOK 1965 - 1966, TMs (Box-folder 5:020)
  EXTENDED PRICE LIST FOR VARIOUS MEDICAL SERVICES & OPERATIONS
- BUDGET EXHIBITS: UVA 1956 - 1958 1956 - 1958, TMs (Box-folder 5:019)
- BUDGET FOR UVA HOSPITAL: CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1952 - 1955, TLS (2), TL, TMs (Box-folder 5:021)
- UVA HOSPITAL BUDGET: CORRESPONDENCE & BUDGET ANALYSES 1961 - 1964, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 5:022)
- UVA HOSPITAL BUDGET: CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1964 - 1970, TLS (3), TL (1), TMs (Box-folder 5:023)
- BIENNIUM BUDGET ESTIMATE, 1962 - 1964, UVA HOSPITAL DIVISION August 15, 1961, TMs (Box-folder 5:024)
  CAPITAL OUTLAY STUDY, 1962 - 1968
- COMPARISON OF 1960 - 1962 APPROPRIATIONS & 1962 - 1964 REQUESTS 1962, TMs (Box-folder 5:025)
- REVISED BUDGET SUMMARY FOR UVA HOSPITAL 1962, TMs (Box-folder 5:026)
- UVA HOSPITAL: MAINTENANCE & OPERATION, BIENNIAL BUDGET, 1964 - 1966 1964 - 1966, TMs (Box-folder 5:028)
- PRELIMINARY BUDGET INFORMATION, 1964-66 BIENNIUM March 27, 1963, TMs (Box-folder 5:027)
  FOR DIVISION OF THE BUDGET-RICHMOND
- ANALYSIS OF GOVERNOR'S RECOMMENDATIONS FOR BIENNIUM BUDGET January 1966, TL, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 5:029)
- COMPARISON OF 1962-64 APPROPRIATIONS & 1964-66 REQUESTS 1964, TMs (Box-folder 5:030)
  GENERAL & SPECIAL FUNDS-UVA HOSPITAL DIVISION
- SUMMARY OF ESTIMATED REVENUES FOR FISCAL YEAR 1967 - 1968 ?1967 - 1968, AMs (xeroxed) (Box-folder 5:031)
- GUIDE FOR MEDICAL EMERGENCY SERVICES FOR THE COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA 1951, TLS (1), Pamphlet (Box-folder 6:001)
  CIVIL DEFENSE PROCEDURES
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA DISASTER PLAN: MASTER COPY April 1953, Mimeograph TMs, TMs (Box-folder 6:002)
- MINUTES OF THE HOSPITAL DISASTER COMMITTEE & PLANS FOR OPERATION DISASTER September 1965, Mimeograph TMs (Box-folder 6:003)
  CIVIL DEFENSE AND EMERGENCY DRILLS
- UVA HOSPITAL DISASTER PLAN FOR CLINICAL SERVICES; EMERGENCY EXPANSION OF HOSPITAL OPERATIONS March 1964, Mimeograph TMs (Box-folder 6:004)
- HEALTH MATERIAL AND FACILITIES PLANNING GUIDE FOR EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT 1965, Pamphlet (Box-folder 6:005)
- SUGGESTIONS FOR DISASTER PROCEDURES AT UVA HOSPITAL February 16, 1968, TL, Floor Plan, TMs (Box-folder 6:006)
- STATE OF VIRGINIA EMERGENCY RESOURCE MANAGEMENT PLAN: RESOURCE MANAGEMENT 1968, TL, Mimeograph TMs (Box-folder 6:007)
- DISASTER ASSISTANCE & HEALTH MOBILIZATION 1968, Pamphlet (4) (Box-folder 6:008)
- STOCKPILE TRANSACTIONS RECORD: PHS EMERGENCY MEDICAL STOCKPILE MATERIAL 1968, TDocs (Box-folder 6:009)
  RE: DISASTER SUPPLIES AT UVA HOSPITAL
- ROTATION & STORAGE AGREEMENTS BETWEEN UVA & MARTHA JEFFERSON HOSPITALS April 1968, TLS (1), TM (1), Pamphlets (2) (Box-folder 6:010)
  RE: EMERGENCY MEDICAL SUPPLIES